hello from Idaho January 17th in Hanoi
City Prudential Life Insurance held a
ceremony to announce a
ten-million-dollar committed to
community social activities in Vietnam
through the Vietnam Prudential fund
Vietnam prudence fund is a commitment of
Prudential not only for social
activities but also of the Vietnam
market this capital will permit Vietnam
Prudential fund to support both these
long-term developed target of Vietnam
and social charitable activities
nationwide the first supported project
will be spent on teenage education and
healthcare speaking in the ceremony mr.
berry stole the chief executive officer
of Asia Prudential corporation said the
American target I'm sorry the important
target in planning activities of the
company is individual and community help
we are supporting not only products and
services for my customers but also
attendants to social community
activities throughout the Asian market
mr. Jack Howell CEO of Vietnam
Prudential company also set prudential
has lived for 11 years in Vietnam a lead
and liability of life company in Vietnam
we are glad to contribute more than in
community activities in Vietnam
therefore contributing to continuous
growth and development in Vietnam
Prudential established the fun prudence
for Vietnam in 2003 it has supported
many charities and commercial community
activities including English teaching
sporting training for teenagers and
information technology scholarships this
is Richard fee good day